Guide to the John Ewart Wallace Sterling, Chancellor of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Series 1
  - Stanford University
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - Cowell Student Health Center Dedication, 1966 May 13 (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - Dedication of Stanford in Britain - Harlaxton, 1966 April 16 (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - Corporate Gifts Committee - Southern California, 1956 May 11 (Box 36, Folder 78)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education, 1966 April 20 (Box 36, Folder 79)
    - California Institute of Technology, 1966 March 28 (Box 36, Folder 80)
    - Bing Nursery School Dedication, 1966 Feb 25 (Box 36, Folder 81)
    - Legion of Honor Award to Dr. Henry S. Kaplan, 1966 Feb 9 (Box 36, Folder 82)
    - Introduction of Dean Bayless Manning - Tuesday Evening Lecture, 1966 Feb 1 (Box 36, Folder 83)
    - Stanford Associates Dinner, 1966 Jan 20 (Box 36, Folder 84)
    - Mothers' Club, 1966 Jan 18 (Box 36, Folder 85)
    - Heritage Fund, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 86)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1966 Jan 11 (Box 36, Folder 87)
    - Report to Board of Trustees, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 88)
    - Stanford Associates Dinner-Bohemian Club for George A. Ditz - "Uncommon Man" Award, 1965 Nov 30 (Box 36, Folder 89)
    - Mills College Founders Day (read by Dean Wert), 1965 Oct 29 (Box 36, Folder 90)
    - New York Parents Luncheon, 1965 Oct 28 (Box 36, Folder 91)
    - Stanford Alumni Meeting - New York, 1965 Oct 27 (Box 36, Folder 92)
    - Planners Luncheon - Phoenix, Los Angeles, San Francisco, New York, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 93)
    - Inauguration of the very Rev. John A Fitter, S.J. as President of Seattle University, 1965 Oct 13 (Box 36, Folder 94)
    - Graduate Convocation, 1965 Sept 26 (Box 36, Folder 95)
    - Foreign Students - Bechtel Center, 1965 Sept 23 (Box 36, Folder 96)
    - Freshman Convocation, 1965 Sept 22 (Box 36, Folder 97)
    - Dean of Students Dinner (RA's, etc.), 1965 Sept 21 (Box 36, Folder 98)
    - International Industrial Conference, 1965 Sept (Box 36, Folder 99)
    - Merner Portrait Unveiling, 1965 Sept 9 (Box 36, Folder 100)
    - International Association of Unversities, 1965 Aug 30-Sept 6 (Box 36, Folder 101)
    - Dedication of the Herbert Hoover Room, 1965 July 20 (Box 36, Folder 102)
    - Stanford Associates Dinner - "Uncommon Man" Award to Herbert Hoover - San Francisco, 1965 July 15 (Box 36, Folder 103)
    - Class Day Activities, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 104)
    - Convocation Honoring E. E. Terman, 1965 May 31 (Box 36, Folder 105)
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 106)
    - AWS Leadership Conference - Campus, 1965 Feb 11 (Box 36, Folder 107)
    - Major Gifts Committee - Los Angeles, 1965 Feb 10 (Box 36, Folder 108)
    - Stanford Faculty Club Dinner Honoring Walter A. Haas, 1965 Feb 5 (Box 36, Folder 109)
    - Mothers' Club, 1965 Jan 19 (Box 36, Folder 110)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1965 Jan 13 (Box 36, Folder 111)
    - Dedication of Storke Student Publications Building, 1964 Nov 20 (Box 36, Folder 112)
    - Parents Day, 1964 Oct 24 (Box 36, Folder 113)
    - Tribute to Herbert Hoover, 1964 Oct 23 (Box 36, Folder 114)
    - Dr. Sterling's 15th Anniversary Dinner Hoover Award - Bohemian Club, 1964 Oct 10 (Box 36, Folder 115)
    - Graduate Convocation, 1964 Sept 27 (Box 36, Folder 116)
    - Dean of Students Dinner (RA's, etc.), 1964 Sept 26 (Box 36, Folder 117)
    - Transfer Assembly, 1964 Sept 26 (Box 36, Folder 118)
    - Freshman Convocation, 1964 Sept 23 (Box 36, Folder 119)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1964 Jan 21 (Box 36, Folder 120)
    - SRI Associates Day, 1963 Dec 5 (Box 36, Folder 121)
    - Memorial Service for John H. Kennedy, 1963 Nov 25 (Box 36, Folder 122)
    - Business and Industry Executives Luncheon - San Diego Yacht Club, 1963 Nov 11 (Box 36, Folder 123)
    - Board of Visitors - Law School, 1963 Oct 4 (Box 36, Folder 124)
    - Law Alumni Luncheon - San Francisco, 1963 Sept 25 (Box 36, Folder 125)
    - Graduate Convocation, 1963 Sept 22 (Box 36, Folder 126)
    - Dean of Students Dinner (RA's, etc.), 1963 Sept 21 (Box 36, Folder 127)
    - Freshman Convocation, 1963 Sept 18 (Box 36, Folder 128)
    - Rotary Club - Berkeley, 1963 Sept 11 (Box 36, Folder 129)
    - Dinner for Al Masters, 1963 Aug 31 (Box 36, Folder 130)
    - Commencement, 1963 June 16 (Box 36, Folder 131)
    - Corporate Luncheons - San Francisco and Los Angeles, 1963 May (Box 36, Folder 132)
    - Dinner for President Gaylord Harnwell - Univeristy of Pennsylvania, 1963 May 9 (Box 36, Folder 133)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1963 Jan 22 (Box 36, Folder 134)
    - Report to Board of Trustees, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Pace Dinner, Oct 18 1962 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Mothers' Club, Oct 16 1962 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Parents Day, Oct 13 1962 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - St. Mary's Convocation (Read by Dr. Brooks), Sept 28 1962 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Dean of Students Dinner (RA's etc.), Sept 22 1962 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Pace Chairman Conference, Sept 22 1962 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Freshman Convocation (Almon E. Roth Honorary Fellowship), Sept 19 1962 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Recorded Statement "Challenging Era", Sept 11 1962 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Sacramento Hosts Breakfast, Sept 7 1962 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Memorial Service for Paul Edwards, July 7 1962 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Commencement, June 17 1962 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Recognition Day, May 11 1962 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - AAUP Dinner "State of the University", April 19 1962 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Founders' Day, March 4 1962 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Trustees' Dinner in Los Angeles, California, Feb 15 1962 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Medical Students, Feb 8 1962 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, Jan 9 1962 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Report to Board of Trustees, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Wiche: "The University in the West Today", Nov 19-21 1961 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, Nov 6 1961 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Mothers' Club, Oct 17 1961 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Luncheon for J. Pearce Mitchell Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce, Oct 16 1961 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Press Club, San Francisco, Sept 29, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Graduate Convocation, Sept. 24 1961 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Freshman Convocation, Sept 20 1961 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Stanford's Overseas Comapuses -- Jews Article for "Vectors" Hughes Aircraft Magazine, Aug 1961 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Loyola University of Los Angeles Commencement, June 11 1961 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Commencement, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - San Jose State College Founders Day "Let us now Praise Famous Men", May 2 1961 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - San Francisco Women's City Club Luncheon, April 21 1961 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Federal Aid to Education Letter enclosure, April 11 1961 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Notes--Report to the Ford Foundation, Mar 22 1961 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - The Executives' Club of Chicago, Mar 23 1961 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Pace Steering Committee Pacific-Union Club, Mar 15 1961 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Tuesday Evening Series Introduction to Jamesa Conant, Mar 7 1961 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - San Diego Rotary Club, Feb 23 1961 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Santa Monica Junior Chamber of Commerce, Jan 28 1961 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Trsutees-Stanford Associates Dinner Los Angeles, Jan 19 1961 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - DJ Russell Dinner (cancelled), Jan 17 1961 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, Jan 10 1961 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - The America-Japan Society Dinner Tokyo, Dec 12 1960 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - University of the Philippines, Dec 6 1960 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Opening of Stanford-in-Italy, Oct 12 1960 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Opening of Stanford-in-France, Oct 8 1960 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Freshman Convocation, Sept 21 1960 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Hoover Birthday Luncheon S.F., Aug 4 1960 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Sloan Scholarship Conference -- Hot Springs, July 14 1960 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Commencement, Jun 12 1960 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Class Day Activities, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - An Educated Person USC Commencement, Jun 9 1960 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Business and Education Fireman's Fund--Bostom, May 26 1960 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Changes and Chances (The Senior Lecture on Higher Education), May 10 1960 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Business School Luncheon Bohemian Club, Mar 24 1960 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Founders' Day, Mar 6 1960 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Tuesday Evening Series Introduction of Carey Croneis, Feb 2 1960 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Mark Ten -- A Decade at Stanford (Draft for President's Report) (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Mothers' Club, Jan 19 1960 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - East Bay Stanford Men's Club, Jan 13 1960 (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, Jan 8 1960 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - What's the Mind and What's the Matter Glass Containers Manufacturers Inst., Nov 12 1959 (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Lloyd Dinkelspiel "Uncommon Man" Award Stanford Associates 25th Birthday, Oct 30 1959 (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - New York Alumni, Oct 29 1959 (Box 37, Folder 66)
    - The Meaning of Education Westover School, Oct 23 1959 (Box 37, Folder 67)
    - Faculty Club, Oct 2 1959 (Box 37, Folder 68)
    - Dean of Students Luncheon, Sept 23 1959 (Box 37, Folder 69)
    - Freshman Convocation, Sept 23 1959 (Box 37, Folder 70)
    - Business Conference Campus, Jul 22 1959 (Box 37, Folder 71)
    - NBC--Chet Huntley Program, Jul 12 & 19 1959 (Box 37, Folder 72)
    - Commencement, Jun 14 1959 (Box 37, Folder 73)
    - Make your Checks Payable too... National Council on Community Foundations, May 22 1959 (Box 37, Folder 74)
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 75)
    - Pioneers Luncheon -- The Golden Spike, May 19 1959 (Box 37, Folder 76)
    - AID -- United Givers, May 6 1959 (Box 37, Folder 77)
    - Pi Sigma Alphia Dinner (Poly Sci), May 14 1959 (Box 37, Folder 78)
    - Inauguration of Thomas A. Spragens Centre College, Kentucky, Apr 21 1959 (Box 37, Folder 79)
    - Volunteer Recognition Day, Apr 11 1959 (Box 37, Folder 80)
    - Pasadena Rotary, Apr 8 1959 (Box 37, Folder 81)
    - Founders' Day, Mar 8 1959 (Box 37, Folder 82)
    - City of Hope Dinner (Karl Weber), 1959 Feb 15 (Box 37, Folder 83)
    - Three Score and Fourteen Years Ago Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce, 1959 Feb 12 (Box 37, Folder 84)
    - KQED Luncheon, 1959 Jan 22 (Box 37, Folder 85)
    - Mothers' Club, 1959 Jan 20 (Box 37, Folder 86)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1959 Jan 8 (Box 37, Folder 87)
    - National Association of Real Estate Boards, 1959 Nov 13 (Box 37, Folder 88)
    - American Association of Medical Clinics, 1959 Oct 3 (Box 37, Folder 89)
    - Inauguration of Clark Kerr, UC, 1958 Sept 29 (Box 37, Folder 90)
    - Board of Governors Stanford Associates, 1958 Sept 26 (Box 37, Folder 91)
    - AWS Leadership Conference, 1958 Sept 25 (Box 37, Folder 92)
    - Dean of Students Luncheon, 1958 Sept 25 (Box 37, Folder 93)
    - Freshman Convocation, 1958 Sept 24 (Box 37, Folder 94)
    - Dinner for Clark Kerr, 1958 Sept 11 (Box 37, Folder 95)
    - Board of Trustees.
      - Trustees, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Trustees, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Letter from George Barbary, 1974 July 29 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Revisions of the Articles of Organization of the Medical School Senate, 1974 July 26 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Stanford University News Service, 1974 June 26 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Statement from University Stanford Employees, 1974 June 4-5 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Stanford University News Service, 1974 June 3 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Letter from Stanford Campus Homeowners Association, 1974 May 31 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Boys Town Center for Youth Development at Stanford, 1974 March 25 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Apartment Units Information, 1974 March 25 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Policy Governing Use of Memorial Church, 1974 Jan. 11 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Memorandum: Major Gift Program Report, 1973 Dec. 14 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Stanford University News Service: ROTC, 1973 Dec. 12 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Letters from Frederic O. Glover, 1973 Sept. (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Memorandum and Board of Trustees Booklet, 1973 Aug.-Sept. (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Appointment of Halsey Royden as Dean of the School of Humanities and Sciences, 1973 Aug. 24 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Board of Trustees Committee, 1973 Aug. 22 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Don't Pay all of the Rent, 1973 Aug. 2 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Letter to Trustees on Actions Suggested by Coopers and Lybrand Auditors, 1973 Aug. 15 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - NLRB Election Procedures and Guidelines for Supervisors, 1973 Mach 27 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Constitution of the Associated Students of Stanford University, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Preliminary Agenda Joint Meeting of the Campaign Executive Committee and the Standford Cabinet Office of the Board of Trustees, 1973 March 13 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - New Founders League of Stanford, 1973 Feb. 27 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - New Founders League of Stanford, 1973 Jan. 18 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Attached Clipping, 1973 Jan. 10 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - New Founders League, 1972 Dec. 14 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - New Founders League Gifts, 1972 Oct.-Nov. (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Letter Concerning Hopkins Marine Station, 1972 Dec. 12-13 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Request to Incorporate the Stanford Business School Alumni Association, 1972 Oct.-Nov. (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Letter from Collman to Brown, 1972 Oct. 18 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Letter from Miller to Brown, 1972 Oct. 13 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Campus Report Volume V Number 2, 1972 Sept. 27 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Stanford Direction, 1972 Aug. (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - Proposed Statement on Faculty Self-Discipline, 1972 Sept. 25 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Stanford University News Service: Use of Student Evaluation Questionnaires, 41972 June 13 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Statement to KZSU radio by President Richard W. Lyman, 1971 May 11 (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - Letter from Lyman to Geyelin, 1972 May 9 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Requests to Halt Projects Funded by Department of defense and to Prevent Economic Hardship, 1972 May 15 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Stanford University News Service: Faculty Political Action Group, 1972 May 15 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - Winds of Freedom Foundation Bulletin #9, 1972 May 2 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - Review of proposed Faculties Expenditures by Three Vice Presidents, 1972 Feb. 18 (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - Allocatable Space, 1972 Feb. 18 (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - Desecration of Memorial Church, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - Ford Foundation Endowments, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - Letter from Moorman to Siena, 1971 Sept. 9 (Box 32, Folder 45)
      - Board of Trustees Committee Assignments, 1971 Aug. 26 (Box 32, Folder 46)
      - Trustees, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 47)
      - Trustees, 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 48)
      - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 49)
      - Trustees, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 50)
      - By-Laws of Board of Trustees (as of 3/11/69), 1969-1976 (Box 32, Folder 51)
      - SRI, 1969 April (Box 32, Folder 52)
      - Trustees, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 53)
      - The Stanford Cabinet, 1971-1975 (Box 32, Folder 54)
      - Ad Hoc Trustee Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 55)
      - Ad Hoc Trustee Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 56)
      - Ad Hoc Trustee Committee (Membership), undated (Box 32, Folder 57)
      - Trustees (Potential), 1968-1971 (Box 32, Folder 58)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) November, 1970, 1970 Nov (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) October, 1970, 1970 Oct (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) September, 1970, 1970 Sep (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) June, 1970, 1970 Jun (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) May, 1970, 1970 May (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) April, 1970, 1970 Apr (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Stanford University Proposed Budget for 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) January 1971, 1971 Jan (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) November 1971, 1971 Nov (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) February 1971, 1971 Feb (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) March 1971, 1971 Mar (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) April 1971, 1971 Apr (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) May 1971, 1971 May (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) June 1971, 1971 Jun (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) September 1971, 1971 Sep (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) October 1971, 1971 Oct (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) November 1971, 1971 Nov (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) January 1972, 1972 Jan (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) February 1972, 1972 Feb (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) March 1972, 1972 Mar (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) April 1972, 1972 Apr (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) May 1972, 1972 May (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) June 1972, 1972 Jun (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) September 1972, 1972 Sep (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) October 1972, 1972 Oct (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) November 1972, 1972 Nov (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) January 1973, 1973 Jan (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Stanford University Report of Gifts Received in March 1973, 1973 Apr (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) March 1973, 1973 Mar (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) February 1973, 1973 Feb (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) March 1970, 1970 Mar (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) February 1970, 1970 Feb (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) January 1970, 1970 Jan (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees) November 1969, 1969 Nov (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Nationwide Support of Higher Education Compared with Stanford's, 1973 Sept. 10 (Box 44A, Folder 1)
      - Operating Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 44A, Folder 2)
      - Settlement of Hospital and Clinic Cost Claims with Medi-cal, 1966-1970 (Box 44A, Folder 3)
      - Status of Gift Support for New Library, 1973 Sept. 5 (Box 44A, Folder 4)
      - Reports of Gift Received Draft, 1973 Sept. 10 (Box 44A, Folder 5)
      - The Wall Street Journal Ads, 1972-1973 (Box 44A, Folder 6)
      - Letter from Grover to Brown, 1973 Sept. 10 (Box 44A, Folder 7)
      - Report of Gifts, 1973 Sept. 11 (Box 44A, Folder 8)
      - Committee on Finance & Development, 1973 Sept. 10 (Box 44A, Folder 9)
      - The Wall Street Journal Ads, 1972-1973 (Box 44A, Folder 10)
      - The Wall Street Journal Ads, 1972-1973 (Box 44A, Folder 11)
      - Report on the State of the Campaign, 1973 Aug. 31 (Box 44A, Folder 12)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1973 June 15 (Box 44A, Folder 13)
      - Preliminary Report on Stanford University Hospital Expansion (Phase II), 1973 June 15 (Box 44A, Folder 14)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1973 May 8 (Box 44A, Folder 15)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1973 April 10 (Box 44A, Folder 16)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 Jan. 8 (Box 44A, Folder 17)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1973 Nov. 13 (Box 44A, Folder 18)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1973 Oct. 9 (Box 44A, Folder 19)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1973 Sept. 11 (Box 44A, Folder 20)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 Feb. 11 (Box 44A, Folder 21)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 March 12 (Box 44A, Folder 22)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 April 9 (Box 44A, Folder 23)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 May 14 (Box 44A, Folder 24)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 June 14 (Box 44A, Folder 25)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 Sept. 10 (Box 44A, Folder 26)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 Nov. 12 (Box 44A, Folder 27)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 Oct. 8 (Box 44A, Folder 28)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1974 Dec. 10 (Box 44A, Folder 29)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 Feb. 10 (Box 44A, Folder 30)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 March 11 (Box 44A, Folder 31)
      - Operating Budget Guidelines, 1975-1976 (Box 44A, Folder 32)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 April 8 (Box 44A, Folder 33)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 May 13 (Box 44A, Folder 34)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 June 13 (Box 44A, Folder 35)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 Sept. 9 (Box 44A, Folder 36)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 Oct. 14 (Box 44A, Folder 37)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 Nov. 11 (Box 44A, Folder 38)
      - Stanford University Agenda (Meeting of the Board of Trustees), 1975 Dec. 9 (Box 44A, Folder 39)
      - Agenda - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1976 Feb 9 (Box 44B, Folder 1)
      - Agenda - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1976 March 9 (Box 44B, Folder 2)
      - Using Cost Analysis in Internal Management in Higher Education, 1976 (Box 44B, Folder 3)
      - Agenda - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1976 April 13 (Box 44B, Folder 4)
      - Stanford University Board of Trustees Meeting Agenda, 1978 June 16 (Box 44B, Folder 5)